leadnetpro.com 2014-02-18

# Lead Net Pro

At LeadNetPro (LNP), protecting your privacy is very important to us. We hope that the following statements will help you in understanding how LNP may collect, use and safeguard any personal information that you may provide to us while visiting our site.

Names, Email Addresses & Other Personal Information Collected Online

* * *

When individual or consumers browse or surf our website, we may at times collect their information when they have taken the time to fill out one of our online forms or have contacted us directly? Any personal information that may be collected would only be submitted by the individual or consumer in regards to receiving more information or possibly by participating in a survey. Additional personal information may be also be collected from individuals or consumers who place an online purchase through our website, and it may also be collected from individuals who decide to participate in our network's affiliate program.

Your Collected Information Is Protected

* * *

Any personal information that may be collected online through our website is always kept private. At no time will any of your personal information ever be shared, sold or viewed by a third party. We value your privacy and have taken the proper measures to assure that your information remains private.

Receiving Communications From Our Website And Affiliates

* * *

When personal information is collected from our website, the individual or consumer who has entered their information is agreeing to receive emails and phone broadcasts from our website and/or affiliates of LNP from time to time. These emails and phone broadcasts may contain specials, newsletters, free reports, free giveaways, important notices, etc. When receiving these emails or phone broadcasts, the individual understands that they have granted us permission to send such emails or to be included in such a phone broadcast when they have filled out our our online forms, have filled out one of our affiliate's online forms, have purchased from us or have become an affiliate of our website.

Questions Regarding Our Privacy Policy

* * *

If a customer has a question regarding our privacy policy or wants further information about our privacy policy, they may contact us by email at (privacy [--at--] leadnetpro.com) for an immediate response. When contacting us please describe your question or concern completely in the text body of the email.

How We Protect Your Information Online

* * *

When and individual fills out a form on or website or participates within our network or our network's affiliate program, their personal information which is collected is stored directly to the servers database. All databases are firewalled, secured and password protected assuring your information remains secure. When placing an order on our website with payment, all orders are process through ssl secure web pages through our secure payment gateway. This information is only collected for the sole purpose of processing your order and remains secure through our merchant's database.

Changes Made To Our Privacy Policy

* * *

From time to time, we make changes to our privacy policy. All changes to our privacy policy will be posted here, and it is the individual's or consumer's responsibility to frequently check our privacy policy for such changes.
